Next, let's talk about your strengths, and I want to make a critical distinction here.
A strength isn't just something you're good at.
You might be excellent at creating complex spreadsheets, but if the process drains every
ounce of energy, that's a learned skill, not a true strength.
A strength is your natural advantage.
It's an activity that you not only do well, but it also energizes you.
It makes you feel authentic and creative and in a state of flow.
Too often, our development plans are about fixing our weaknesses.
An athlete flips that script.
They focus on mastering and deploying their strengths.
They find roles and projects where they can operate from their zone of genius as often
as possible.
This is the fastest path to excellence and impact.
We know you may have heard about focusing on strengths before.
The difference in this experience is that we connect your strengths to your energy.
An athlete doesn't just do what they're good at.
They build their work and life around things that make them feel the most alive.
Your playbook has a drill designed to help you identify the unique talents and highest
value that you bring to the table.
Things that when you do them, you feel most alive and most powerful.